For ages…
Alien locked up their
prisoners in humans' bodies.
But humans were not aware of this.
Sometimes prisoners escaped the humans…
like a jailbreak.
Over there!
A monster came from that woman's body!
Kill her!
That way!
The sky is opening!
Prisoner #78A47.
Escaped its body
268 seconds ago.
The human is dying.
Need to catch it before
it enters another human.
Find its location.
40 meters ahead.
moving slowly.
35... 30...
Approaching.
Look out!
Don't worry.
I'm okay!
I didn't ask.
The prisoner is re-entering the human!
Extracting prisoner.
More prisoners will escape.
I am not the last.
The world you manage is unstable.
Mission complete.
Time to return.
Save my baby.
It's a baby.
We don't concern
ourselves with human affairs.
Did you hear. baby?
Sorry. but we don't concern
ourselves with human affairs.
Hold on.
Kill the monster's baby!
Shooting an arrow?
At a baby?
Catch it!
You creep!
Time to go back.
-Should we take her?
-She'll die here.
No interacting with humans.
Look.
She wants to come!
And why mimic me like that?
Too uncanny a resemblance?
Wait.
The baby's future!
Don't pretend you saw her future.
Let's return.
before the gate closes.
Sure. we'd better go.
Why are you sitting there?
Right. how silly of me.
Let's go!
The alien prisoners existed
in various time periods…
And it was Guard and
Thunder's job to manage them.
This was the 7th escape…
And all had been handled smoothly.
But that day was a bit different.
What?
What is this?
How'd she get there?
-What did you do?
-Nothing...
Well... it's like...
-Where are you going?
-I'm not going anywhere.
Why'd you bring the baby?
My mistake...
Should we kill her?
After bringing her here?
What was I thinking?
Let's experiment on her.
Stimulate parts of her brain.
Then we can learn more about humans.
-So first...
-First what?
How about bringing her inside?
Me?
Yeah!
What does she eat?
All mammals drink their mother's milk.
Ingredients; Lactose. lipids. protein.
They sell that in stores.
Shall we begin on her brain?
We'll just throw her away later.
-Of course.
-Prepare to report.
Prisoner #78A47.
The 7th escaped prisoner has been detained.
Analyzing reason for escape.
Sometimes the human brain
becomes aware of the prisoner.
Humans could be far more
complicated than we estimated.
Hey.
How much longer do
we have to stay on Earth?
No word on that.
The next transport ship
arrives in 10 years. 8 months.
-End of transmission.
10 years and 8 months...
Oh my.
ALIENOID
(1391. GORYEO DYNASTY)
Ever caught the mist over
a river as the sun is setting?
Is that the magic of a dosa?
Catching mist in your hand?
More than that...
If I put my hand inside.
what is hand and what is mist?
I become one with the mist!
Dosa. just show us your magic.
Magic is not to be done on a whim.
Magic is…
To call forth rain from a blue sky!
But who wants rain on a day like this.
so no rain.
To call forth a gust of wind!
And with enough training.
nothing can hurt you.
-Nothing?
-Sure.
Strike me with that. here.
Is this okay. too?
A knife?
And quite deep!
Get me a cloth.
-I'll pull it out.
-No. don't!
I said don't pull it out!
Oh no.
-I'm fine.
-For a dosa. this is...
Thieves have entered my Lord's home!
I hear a famous dosa is here?
Right here!
There's a reward. will you go?
Is it these 3 men?
That's right!
Since there's a reward...
They're on the run.
A bell.
Any temple nearby?
That way!
What are you running away from?
Evil deeds are wrong. however small.
As humans.
don't you know shame?
I. the dosa Marvelous Muruk will
pass judgment on behalf of heaven.
What's this?
We are the fabulous shaman dosa.
Marvelous Muruk?
You're a hack who conjures cats!
20 bolts of cotton!
We'll collect the bounty.
so step aside. hack!
Who's a hack?
Besides. there are
rules in this line of work...
The one who saw them
first has precedence. right?
I've been...
You tie yourselves up.
Must I burst your eardrums to do?
-Where are you from anyway?
-You again?
The bounty's mine. I tell you.
I'll show you!
Prajna-paramita!
Right Paw. Left Paw. come forth!
Is this how it's done?
You really think you can
mimic my clan's century-old...
The bounty for 3 thieves
is 20 bolts of cotton.
Hey Muruk! There's a new wanted list.
-I see it.
-Who should I catch this time?
Anyone with a high bounty?
Look at these scoundrels!
The bounties are high this time.
Wow. 50 bolts of cotton for
the Girl Who Shoots Thunder?
Divine Blade.
Bounty... 2000 bolts?
Hold on. I think I saw...
Muruk?
You okay?
Another headache?
This is a detailed drawing.
meaning someone saw it.
Dog Turd.
He's in prison. as you know.
Still there?
Then I'll have to pay him a visit.
Will Dog Turd tell you anything?
You put him in there.
Don't worry.
I know him well.
Oh my. sir!
This is Dog Turd's son.
Say hello.
He's been begging to see
his father before he dies.
Look at you. working here day and night.
-Have a drink.
-I can't refuse a taste of this.
That hits the spot.
Instead of food.
Give your dad a bowl of this.
How can we ever repay you?
Oh my!
Dog Turd is lucky to see
his son before dying.
-Oh Father!
-Did I have a son?
Father.
your son Muruk is here!
Muruk. you son of a cow!
The arm you broke
still hasn't healed!
Every night I grind my teeth
and curse your name!
He's so overjoyed.
listen to him!
Everything heals with time.
why grind your teeth?
What's the Divine Blade?
You think I'll tell you
for a lousy cup of liquor?
A plum blossom will
never sell its fragrance!
Not even on the verge of death!
The key to your cell. Father.
My precious son!
What's the Divine Blade?
On the 5th day of August this year.
a fisherman found a strange knife
in the river near Yellow Mountain.
There was a jewel in it.
First he asked a blacksmith
to pull out the jewel.
but it wouldn't come
loose even with a hammer.
A lame man standing
nearby was hit in the chest…
Then he stood up with no cane.
For sure. that item is not of this world.
It came from heaven.
Then who has the blade now?
Well... It was bought by
Master Hyun of Yellow Mountain.
Now he runs an inn called Big Rahn.
Better hurry then. I'll be going. Father!
Careful!
Master Hyun is the nation's greatest dosa.
I'm a dosa too. you know.
Oh Father. don't worry!
You say you're a dosa.
but I've never seen you train.
Two kinds of training.
Daily effort or sudden enlightenment.
-I'm the second type.
-That's how I call you forth to serve me.
-Serve you?
-That's what you think?
It's only because of that fan.
You can't even use it properly.
Two powerful swords are in there.
but you can't pull them out.
I can't?
That's what you think?
If I take one out.
you're dead!
Should I? I'm doing it!
Two swords!
They're finally coming out?
Prajna-paramita!
You see? See it?
Heavy. right?
Next time!
-Too many people around.
-Don't be upset. You'll do it soon.
Soon? He'll turn 60 first.
Go back in the fan and live in there. then.
Now. don't be inhumane.
-Who's the human?
-There goes your temper.
Have a drink.
Rice wine. please!
I'm telling you. Right Paw's
mouth works faster than his brain.
Ma'am. where is Big Rahn Inn?
Around that corner.
Hey. Right Paw.
That man's clothes are pretty odd.
Right.
Big Rahn Inn.
Give me some luck!
A one or a two!
Got you!
Let me ask something.
I heard some Master Hyun fellow
from Yellow Mountain is here.
Is he?
Any thought of selling that fan?
This is precious. it's not for sale.
Why do you laugh?
Is that precious thing yours.
Did you steal it?
Fate is a mysterious thing.
You think I'm a thief.
you doddering old man?
Don't you know who he is?
Speak with respect!
Master Hyun?
Mundra mundra
mahabaruka heruka!
Using strength again.
Rise with your mind.
Believe nothing pushes down on you.
What nonsense!
Do you know me?
Why would I know a nobody like you?
From now on.
don't put your nose in important business.
Back to your drinks. everyone!
Right paw! Left paw!
Muruk!
-Did the guest arrive?
-Yes. this is him.
Hey. pull me up!
Murderer.
No name.
You say you know what this is for?
Of course.
How do you know?
It belongs to us.
-Us?
-Yes.
Who is 'us'?
Where did he go?
Master Hyun? Upstairs.
Do you know him already?
How would I know that old man?
What? I think that's Dog Turd.
Dog Turd!
Thought I could smell something.
Dang it! He knows the Divine Blade is here.
Prajna-paramita!
Master Hyun!
Are you okay?
Stay out of these affairs.
Stay out?
What do you...?
Murderer.
Muruk!
Dog Turd ran off with the blade!
A late lunch. I see?
Muruk. you son of a cow!
-You okay?
-I'm fine.
Why. because you stole off with the blade?
No. not that.
What?
Where is it?
The monster!
It's coming!
Hurry and run away!
Where's Muruk?
-Muruk!
Where did he go?
Here!
Muruk!
Muruk?
Wake up!
Where did he go?
How'd he vanish like that?
Vanish?
You've been here for hours.
And Dog Turd ran off.
You okay?
My back feels broken.
But why does my cheek hurt?
Did someone hit me. Right Paw?
Me? No way!
Why would I?
There's something there!
-What?
-Where?
What is that? A rock?
Can a rock glow like that?
Did it appear before me because I'm a dosa?
The river's low because of the drought.
It's making noise!
Someone's there.
Who is it?
We called you because
your daughter has a problem.
Recently she went to
the police to report you.
They said. "Why are you here?"
She told them you stole her as a baby.
That her memory is good because
you experimented on her brain.
-Play the video.
-Yes.
The police gave us this.
Why'd your dad experiment on your brain?
Is he a doctor?
No.
Actually he's not my dad.
He's a robot.
Like a cyborg.
That sounds serious.
How'd you find out?
Good question.
I took a video last night.
But I think sometimes it's.
Thunder disguised as my dad.
Who's Thunder?
The car my dad drives.
He can turn into my dad.
I saw it when I was a kid.
He deleted it already.
I was careless.
I'll come back with more evidence.
Then the police said she
jumped from the 3rd floor.
How about that?
Delete the video that principal watched.
I already did.
Beware of the woman stalking you.
-Who? -The one in yellow.
Hello! Are you Ean's dad?
I'm Min-sun's aunt.
I see.
Min-sun and Ean are so close.
they can't live without each other.
Friends for life. I guess?
Yes.
Coffee?
I saw you from afar a few times.
so thought I'd say hello.
How old are you?
Our ages seem similar.
Your dad is really good-looking. huh?
He is.
Doesn't resemble me.
But I don't think your aunt
stands a chance.
It's okay. look at her.
-She never gives up.
-It's best when it's hot.
Aunt!
Hi Min-sun!
Are you Ean?
Wow. so cute.
The spitting image of your dad!
These are homemade burgers.
eat them with Ean.
You won't believe how good they are.
Bye!
-Let's go!
-Okay.
What?
What did the principal say?
You curious about the
texting I do with my friend?
No.
Okay.
Thanks. Thunder!
Who are you talking to?
To him.
Cars can't talk.
I talked to him when I was young. for sure.
Finally. a photo with Dad!
You talk to her behind my back?
No. never.
Of course. I did when she was young.
Can she remember that?
But why's my name Thunder?
Thank you for your purchase.
Hey!
Not sure I like it.
Quiet!
Why'd she give me that name?
Read out the new message.
The 19th transport of
prisoners is underway.
107 prisoners.
Transport ship to reach Earth in 18 hours.
Transport of prisoners? What's that?
Location?
Not yet determined.
Searching for a place where
107 hosts will be gathered.
18 hours is tomorrow...
Every night at 9PM.
the lights go out and Dad disappears.
Lights out!
Thunder!
Ignoring me?
Forget it.
Did the recording come out okay?
What's this?
No...
No. you'll be hurt!
-Thunder!
-This is what I saw as a kid.
But why's my name Thunder?
You don't like it?
I'm starting to like it.
What are you?
Where do you come from?
You can say I'm a program.
I process information. and
can change into anything.
What should I be?
Your dad?
Dad?
No way.
Is this a hologram?
It's real.
You can feel it.
As for where I came from...
Here!
You really came from there?
You and Dad are aliens?
We think you're the alien.
Then are you Dad's servant?
Not a servant!
We're on equal footing.
He's a fighting model. I'm pacifist.
Is your home far away?
Close and far are all relative.
Einstein!
-What?
-Look at you.
-You're all grown up!
-I even named you! -Really?
And you stock our home's
vending machine every day?
Yeah!
You eat a lot of dried fish these days.
-That's right. I'm hooked!
-You're hooked!
But where's the prisoner
transport taking place?
Just got a message saying Jisan Hospital.
SOS signal!
Transport location leaked to a human.
You traitor.
I didn't betray you.
I just overheard.
Your dad's coming.
Get out. quick!
Wait.
Where did I come from?
I'll tell you next time.
-Go. quick!
-Tell me now.
Where am I from?
The past.
642 years ago!
And forget about Jisan Hospital!
Please!
What was the SOS signal?
We have a new message.
The transport ship will arrive 8.2
km to the east at Jisan Hospital.
Jisan Hospital.
You okay?
I'm fine.
What are you shooting?
Just recording people.
Never know what might happen.
You worry a lot.
What do you think will happen?
Right now...
nothing's happened. so I don't know.
Wait!
If what you're worried
about happens. call me.
I'm a cop.
We'll see.
Look at the cloud. it's so pretty.
-Wow!
-Look at the cloud!
Wow!
The transport ship has arrived.
Ready to implant prisoners in humans.
What is this?
What?
Come on!
Why are you here?
What was I doing in there?
Big Rahn Inn.
Poor Master Hyun...
Our old pal is dead!
After he said he'd give us the blade.
Don't cry. Mr. Blue.
He said he'd meet a man
who knew the blade's origin.
That man is the culprit.
Right. Madam Black.
Which dosa did this?
The culprit is no dosa.
Something pierced Master Hyun
and punctured the door.
A wind bolt?
Doesn't taste like it.
A tentacle?
-A monster?
-A monster is here?
How extraordinary.
Just as we were called to Secret Temple.
Remember that rumor?
A monster lives in Secret Temple?
We were called to Secret Temple.
If so. let's go.
The Sorcerers of Twin Peaks?
-Right!
-The Married Masters?
We're not married. mister.
They say the murderer
lived here for 10 years.
Such a dangerous...
-You're going in?
-Yeah.
Have you no fear?
The Divine Blade is at Big Rahn Inn.
Bring it to me.
-Jajang.
-Jajang?
The chief of Secret Temple?
Why do they want the blade?
There's a strange painting here.
Yeah. well...
That's what we saw in the river!
The man living here is really crazy.
Where did he see these?
Secret Temple.
Don't you have ears?
How long must we knock?
Is Jajang in?
Tell him the Sorcerers
of Twin Peaks are here.
The monster rumor started when.
Jajang arrived 10 years ago.
So what is this Jajang fellow?
Let's take stock of the man.
while trying to sell our goods.
The sorcerers Madam Black and Mr. Blue...
Nice to meet you. Jajang.
Your dignity emanates
from your mask.
Indeed.
It's the famous Madam Black and Mr. Blue.
Thank you for coming.
You requested our goods.
how could we refuse?
Let's begin.
This item makes the products
we invented before look like toys.
This is no ordinary charm.
it can make a copy of myself. Look!
If you don't like that.
we have other charms.
Like the "Freeze!" charm.
If you buy one.
we'll add 20 more.
I see.
This is our enchanted bronze mirror.
Those paper charms can't compare.
A wondrous mirror that
reflects one's true nature.
When I look into my soul…
So divine and beautiful.
Shall we look into yours?
Faces do not matter in Secret Temple.
Certainly not.
But this mirror has other properties.
Small objects can be made large.
If a cup is too small. make it into a bowl.
Now imagine putting
one's fist through this.
Forgive me. Buddha!
If my fist goes in. this
building will collapse.
That's enough.
How remarkable that humans
can create such objects.
That's why they call us sorcerers.
This mirror was made from
1000-year old Scythian copper
engraved and polished
for more than 15 years.
Took 3 years just to make it sparkle.
-Can't put a price on that.
-But if one were to try.
Madam Black?
70 silver coins. Mr. Blue.
No haggling over that.
First. have some tea.
If you don't love it at
first sight. we won't sell it.
-Never mind the tea.
-We must go.
The Divine Blade keeps
changing hands. we intend to find it.
-Very nice to meet you.
-You know where the Blade is?
Of course. at Lord Choi's residence.
The daughter's wedding is today.
and Dog Turd sold them the Blade.
Shall we help you?
We won't be lonely then.
Who are you to block my path?
The groom's got a nice mustache.
Yeah.
A mustache gives you
flair. but mine won't grow.
Listen. you!
What are you doing?
Come on down.
Let me borrow that mustache.
-My mustache?
-Yes.
He's here! He's here!
The bridegroom's here!
He's arrived!
Play the music!
Let the wedding begin!
Bridegroom. please enter!
That's a handsome bridegroom!
Make a bow!
Is it in that box?
I think so.
Bride and groom. greet each other
and drink.
This one's got spirit!
What comes off first?
What's first...?
So beautiful!
But have we met before?
Hardly.
So what comes off first...
What is this?
Don't let small things distract
you from your great task.
First. warm up with some liquor.
Yes. let's do that.
Meow!
Why pester him when he's enjoying himself?
He came here to work!
Is this the time to flirt
with an innocent maiden?
This place has fish!
Isn't that snapper?
So precious...
Eat this first. okay?
The head of a snapper is so good.
especially in autumn.
So it is!
Meow!
I'll just visit the toilet.
I can hardly believe
a lady like you is my bride.
Such a cute bridegroom.
Why pester me?
It's bad luck to hurry.
Muruk!
The wedding gifts are in the family shrine.
-All right. fine.
-Did you drink?
Just one cup!
What's wrong with me?
We are the sorcerers of Twin Peaks.
From now. no one is allowed to leave!
Hey. the feast is over!
Everyone step aside.
Jajang's men will erect a fire barrier.
so do not cross that line!
Otherwise. you may die!
What are you doing?
Stop them. now!
How dare you!
How dare you third-rate dosa cause a scene?
This is a wedding day.
I'll kill...
Lord Choi?
Yes?
Lord Choi.
Bring the Divine Blade.
Yes. of course.
My lady!
-What is the bride doing here?
-Mistress!
Who did this to my baby!
Some bitch tied me up!
Some bitch?
Then who's in the bridal chamber?
I had too much liquor.
Bring the Divine Blade
from my hidden chest!
Yes!
Who are you?
A fake bride?
You don't look like a real groom. either.
Did you
slip something in my cup?
Yeah.
Yeah?
You won't die. Don't worry.
Antidote...
You have an antidote?
Nothing like that.
No?
Get some sleep. you'll be fine.
I'll take them out.
Can't let them steal what's mine.
You can do it! Just do it!
You're completely mad.
I'm not your real bride…
But I'll keep this memory.
Right Paw! Left Paw!
Stay back!
That wicked girl is shooting thunder!
Let's use the curtain.
Give it to them.
Over here.
Yes!
Don't move.
You think you can take that?
I was cut by the blade!
Me too!
Got you. wench!
Put her in the palanquin.
Yes!
Muruk!
I was drugged.
-The blade?
-It's gone. We failed.
-Massage his arms.
-What would you do without us?
I whistled for you!
Are you there. bridegroom?
Hide. quick!
-Grab that! -The black thing!
-A black thing? -Yeah.
A black thing? This?
What is this thing?
What is this black thing?
Ean!
Why weren't you in school?
I ran away.
Can I sleep over?
Oh my god!
This was really at the hospital?
You shot it yourself?
Yeah.
What's going in people's heads?
Is your dad controlling it?
Aunt!
Yeah?
I'm not eavesdropping.
Just walking by.
I'm walking by!
Arriving at Min-sun's home.
I don't know how to talk to humans.
You go.
Me? Which one of me?
-Me! I'll go. -I want to persuade humans!
-Ever talked to a human?
-No. right?
-You never let me.
I know about humans. I'll go.
Stop.
You know about romance?
-Ever talked to a woman?
-The key to conversation is simple.
Listen closely.
then catch them off guard.
Ever done it before?
Then should we all go?
No. just one of you.
-You go.
-Okay!
Keep the conversation short. And bring Ean.
Short! That's right.
Shall we go?
To catch her off guard.
Hello.
I know everything.
That Ean is here?
That. of course.
-And I know you like me.
-What?
Yeah.
I was going to call you.
It's okay if I call?
That's the purpose of a phone.
Shall I call Ean down from upstairs?
We understand each other.
What was your name?
I'm Min Gaelin.
Min...?
I know. it's a odd name for a woman.
I had a lot of nicknames as a kid.
Gaelic. Alien...
Min-sun!
Ms. Min Gaelin!
Let me tell you.
You're lucky.
You're not an alien.
Thank you.
Hi.
Let's go.
What was put in the people at the hospital?
What was it?
Time for a scolding.
Don't you know humans yet?
What you hide. they try to find out.
Ean. Sit down.
We'll answer just 3 questions.
Okay? Go.
What did you put in the people?
So. we've been locking up
our prisoners on Earth for ages.
-Right?
-Hey!
-Calm down.
-It's the same as here.
Wars were fought.
the population declined.
Everyone wanted peace.
and we didn't kill criminals.
But a problem came up.
Mutants appeared.
Destructive mutants that preferred
killing over life and peace.
So?
So we needed a prison.
Somewhere far. far away.
small and safe.
A prison for memories. too.
The human brain.
We put the prisoner there.
and when the human dies. it perishes.
That's their punishment.
But humans didn't agree.
to having something in them.
Did you agree to be born?
Still. you shouldn't treat humans that way.
-Don't look down on us.
-You've gotten so smart. Ean!
That's thanks to me.
You be quiet.
Next question.
-Can the prisoners escape?
-If they do. they don't last long.
It's a different atmosphere.
After 5 minutes
they have to go back in.
If they escape. I lock them up again.
-Where?
-Here.
We had this in our home?
If they escape. do they kill people?
It's my duty to prevent that.
So you're here to protect humans.
I'm a guard in charge of prisoners.
I don't concern myself with humans.
No more questions.
Then why do you live with me?
No more questions!
Thunder. can I sleep here?
Thanks.
How long have you been on Earth?
Aren't you lonely?
Why did you take me in?
If we didn't…
You would've died.
Good night. Ean.
Good night. Thunder.
Suspect is approaching.
Everyone stand by.
He's running away!
Chase him!
Freeze!
The first bullet's a blank!
What a waste!
Don't shoot me!
Don't shoot!
-Have a good day.
-Thank you.
-Hey Moon! -Yes?
-What did I tell you about the use of guns?
It's just for show.
throw the gun. don't shoot it.
Hey. if you shoot.
don't miss!
How can a detective be so timid?
Stop it. Sorry.
Your name and address.
Write them here.
This is Lee Wan-gyu. Violent Crimes.
So where are the rest of the drugs?
-I hid them in the bike on the 2nd floor.
-The bike on the 2nd floor?
Shit.
Way to use your head.
Ta-da!
What's this?
Go on down.
Attorney Cho?
Are you okay?
Urgent message received.
"You are in danger.
A spacecraft is headed to Earth."
"You are in danger."
Something headed to Earth?
What are you doing?
What's with you?
Something is controlling me!
It's hacking my data!
Who's hacking into you?
It's checking the prisoner records.
It found him!
One human.
Name. Moon Do-seok.
Moon was captured on CCTV. and
his fingerprints are on the weapon.
He's not answering his phone.
Detective Lee.
What is that?
Ean. get out.
No.
I want to see the work you do.
Get out.
No. I'm part of this family too.
Urgent message.
The spacecraft is approaching.
Then hold on.
It's accessing Moon's location!
Trace the location of the spacecraft.
Dad. what is all this?
Sit down.
Moon!
Where are you?
Who are you?
How'd you get in here?
What is that?
Step aside. police.
Where's Moon?
The 21st floor elevator.
Something is approaching him.
Moon!
The great Controller is locked inside you.
What are you?
Controller. I came to set you free.
Using Guard's energy.
Are you ready?
Who's the prisoner in Moon's body?
Prisoner #197A.
Convicted as...
The Controller.
The Controller?
Who sowed rebellion and
destruction on our planet.
The leader of the prisoners.
The ship came to free him?
What's his goal?
Is it chasing me?
Can you hear me. Controller?
Are you ready to break free?
Replace the Earth's atmosphere.
Free all of the prisoners.
Only you can save the prisoners.
Soon. now...
What the hell is he?
Now. protect Ean. Thunder!
Get ready.
Okay! Ean. hold on!
He's in front.
Let's knock him down.
Raise the energy.
-We got him!
-Not yet.
His shield is too strong.
Raise the energy again.
Maximize the shield!
Careful. he's on our tail.
What's his weak point?
There's only one place where
his exterior meets the interior.
His red heart.
Shoot him there.
and he'll malfunction.
It opens when he attacks!
People are going to get hurt.
Get away from the city!
Get ready!
Now! Fire!
The red heart is moving.
Emergency!
We've been hit!
Warning! We're falling!
Raise the energy again!
We need more time!
More time!
Mission complete.
Energy link successful.
Break out detected.
The Controller is self-aware!
Break out complete.
I'll blow up Guard and myself.
Warning!
Guard's life support system is destroyed!
Ean! Wait inside!
Life force at 17. 16. 14...
Danger level is high.
Life force restoration starts.
Life force restoration in progress...
37... 38...
My energy is dropping.
Chase after the Controller.
Find out what he wants.
Okay.
stay still!
The Controller is operating the spacecraft.
Haava!
It's filled with haava!
Haava?
Our planet's atmosphere?
Different than Earth's.
If they burst.
Earth's atmosphere will become like ours.
If the prisoners breathe it.
they'll all break free.
And the humans will all die.
Earth will be finished.
I have to stop him!
Hurry!
Access the energy and stop the haava!
I know!
Your life force is falling again!
I need to stop the haava!
Catch the Controller. before
he enters another body!
Ean. are you okay?
What is that?
One of the prisoners.
The Controller vanished.
Get inside the car.
Emergency!
Two of the haava escaped.
I'll get them first.
Find them quickly!
We can't let them blow up.
Detonate the haava.
Wake the prisoners in this district.
Open your eyes! Wake up!
Why won't the belt come off?
I retrieved one haava.
Save the people first!
I'm going!
Ean. let's go!
You go home!
Thunder!
Can't let them steal the haava.
You go now.
I'll find the Controller.
People dying.
The exploding red haava.
It's never once left my
mind these past 10 years.
Who are you?
You're all grown up.
Remember?
10 years ago we came here together.
Even with the Divine
Blade. you can't escape here.
Right. we need the ship.
Where is it?
I don't know.
No. you know.
That's why you sought the blade.
Where is it?
You should learn what prison is like.
Think hard about how you can
last a little longer in there.
Hey.
Let's talk later.
We've got plenty of time.
We're trapped in time.
To go back. we need to find the Controller.
Only he can handle that energy.
I killed Master Hyun.
but nothing came out.
Whose body holds the Controller?
There were 4 humans present on that day.
You pierced Master Hyun. but he died.
Mr. Blue and Madam Black touched
the energy. but Controller didn't emerge.
We must find the last one.
It's okay.
She's deaf and mute.
Why stay in that diseased body?
Enter a healthy one.
I'll lose my memory.
I don't want to go back to prison.
You okay. Muruk?
But are we entering Secret
Temple to save that girl?
Girl?
Who?
The Divine Blade's reward has shot up!
What could this thing be anyway?
Right. the reward is what's important.
So good to see Muruk thinking practically.
You're all grown up now!
Who do you think I am?
They're coming.
Let's get to work.
Mundra mundra
mahabaruka heruka!
Why are you fools so late?
You found what we sent you for?
They're waiting in the main hall.
Yes.
Don't dawdle. move!
Yes!
-We're going!
-On our way!
I said. the main hall!
That way!
Our medicine is here.
The 3 errand men have returned.
You found the red antler mushroom?
-Yes.
-Give it here.
Hand it over.
That poison mushroom
must be chewed before applying.
Who is the poison specialist?
It's this very man.
Yes... I... am?
Go ahead. chew it!
Don't stop!
Chew it faster.
To mix with saliva.
That's the way.
Who has the letter sent to me?
Me?
This?
Spit it in here.
That's the best chewed mushroom ever!
The iron wagon surfaced
in a river by Big Rahn Inn.
I've found it now!
Why is the energy reacting?
It's shining light on its own.
The sun. moon and stars only can do.
The light's gone again.
But why does the Girl Who
Shoots Thunder seek it?
But a day after being pierced by the Blade.
there's no change in either of you?
My aching knee has improved.
My knee. too!
Stay the night to heal your wounds.
Serve them our special rice.
-Yes.
-Why don't the three of you go?
Jajang acts like
he owns that blade.
-Did you see the Blade?
-Yes!
Let's sneak in tonight.
Of course!
The Blade is ours now!
-You there! -Yes?
-Bring this to her.
There's a fire barrier at the rear
courtyard. push it through the gap.
-Don't speak to the girl. -Yes!
-You two! -Yes? -You wash the dishes.
Now where's the rear courtyard?
Is it the nice weather
that makes the birds sing so?
Let's take a look.
So this is the fire barrier!
And here's the gap.
But how did they create this?
Does it come from this fire?
Then...
-It won't go out.
-Oh my...
Hey!
Are you that thief?
Thief?
I'm the husband bringing your food.
Can you eat these flowers?
Are you a fool?
Flowers are for the eyes to consume.
You drugged me and rushed
off bravely. so why are you here?
Then why are you here?
To steal the Divine Blade?
What do you mean?
My house is nearby.
Did you steal it?
Not yet.
But I saw it just now. and it glowed
as if to say. "Steal me!"
It did? In front of you?
Well. in the main hall.
about this far away.
But I think I saw it when
I was young. my memory is hazy.
No need to tell me your life story.
I'm not your real wife.
But listen.
My lost memory seems
connected to that blade somehow.
You say it's yours?
What is that thing?
Where'd it come from?
If I told you. would you understand?
Hey. thief. If you're a dosa.
just focus on training.
Don't try to make money off the Blade.
I knew you'd say that.
Then is this related to it?
Where did this come from?
-How does the thunder come out?
-Don't pull it!
Give me my gun.
Then tell me where the blade came from.
The future.
Future?
Future
I think I've been there.
The village across the river?
Wait.
That's not what you mean.
The time to come?
Precisely 630 years in the future.
What do you think?
I'm learning a lot today.
"What do you think?"
Add that. and I'm speechless.
That's the way a person should lie!
-So people live there now?
-Yeah.
How can that be?
-Wait. wait! The fire!
-Give me my gun.
Hey. I'm on fire!
It's hot!
What's that noise there?
The Blade is mine. then!
Who were you talking to?
Let's go!
Records of Master Hyun.
And the girl?
We poisoned her food.
so she must be dying now.
-Bury her.
-With the two sorcerers.
Yes. Jajang.
And bring me the blade.
Yes.
How long since we've
had this delicious rice?
Over a decade.
Let's eat. and...
Poisoned rice?
Jajang. that scoundrel!
Do power breathing.
Before paralysis sets in.
Get the antidote...
The paralysis…
Came!
Hurry!
Pick it up!
Pull him up!
Poisoned rice...
Antidote...
Antidote? What antidote?
Yes!
The coffin is here!
Whose coffin?
Our coffin!
Who goes there?
Poisoned rice!
Antidote!
Poisoned rice?
Yes!
I brought rice to that girl.
Antidote?
That scoundrel!
Mailahum Muharamundur Banyabaramil!
Up there!
Sorry. guys.
Banyabaramil!
Muruk!
Chase after him.
The back garden!
Catch him!
Hot!
Hot! Fire!
Hurry! Antidote!
Hair on fire!
Hot!!
Wiping your mouth?
I'll let it slide.
Need to find out why Jajang poisoned us.
Let's go.
Get him!
Just a minute!
I'll divert them.
Muruk! This way.
Over there! Get him!
Whoops!
Catch him!
I need to go back.
I won't be long.
No. Muruk!
That girl might die.
Muruk. you might die.
It's okay.
I'll be right back.
Banyabaramil!
Antidote.
I brought the antidote.
I'm sorry.
I brought you poisoned rice.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
You're doing well.
You'll be okay.
Bury her. and throw him in the river.
Prepare the palanquin.
I'm going back to where I came from.
It's not clear where
this red gas came from.
or what it is.
Experts say the polluted zone
no longer resembles Earth.
One can even describe it as
the atmosphere of an alien planet.
The polluted zone has stopped expanding...
What is that?
That's the source of our energy.
That blade powers everything.
That blade can wake up prisoners.
and it can move you through time.
Time doesn't flow.
it is simultaneous.
We used this energy to bring you here. too.
Then can we go back in time to save people?
That has no meaning.
Their universe is already finished.
And the energy is very unstable now.
How unstable?
I see the future.
In fragments. disordered...
Help the Controller.
I'll give you a weapon.
There are survivors here.
but they're floating.
I'm saying they're floating in air!
What's happening?
Don't touch!
I saw myself as an adult.
Long time no see.
Don't think you'll
last long in that body.
I can't move to another body yet.
I'll forget who I am.
Forget…
We see ambulances
entering the polluted zone.
The survivor's identities are not known.
but after decontamination.
they will be quarantined.
Once again.
two survivors have...
Two prisoners broke free in the haava.
They're coming this way.
We need to send Ean away.
We see ambulances
entering the polluted zone...
That thing which burst was like a virus?
It killed people.
It was just a small one.
There are many left.
In there?
But are you okay?
I'm okay.
I need to carry those into space.
I'll take the escaped prisoners too.
-Ean. about your mother.
-I need to tell you something.
My mother?
I killed your mother.
Why?
There was a prisoner
inside her. and it escaped.
We took you because we needed you.
With you.
we could mix with humans easily.
But now you're a burden.
Will you leave this home?
Liar!
Robots don't lie.
I'll leave!
Damn robot.
Not even human.
Then send me back to where I came from.
Your life force is at 9%.
-Your chances of winning...
-Don't tell me.
I know already.
You take Ean. Thunder.
To Min-sun's house.
Okay.
What did you write on the note?
Run away. you fool.
Thunder.
leave one last message.
It was wrong to put prisoners into humans.
Guard will never run away.
Even if he dies fighting.
He's programmed that way.
What is life force?
His remaining life.
It's dropping.
Now it's at 8%.
His chance of winning
the battle is 1%.
Let's turn back. Thunder.
We can't!
I need to leave you at your destination.
Dad needs you.
Turn the car around!
You can't help him.
It's what my heart wants.
Let's go to Dad.
Where did he go?
The departure signal is on.
He wants to take us to space?
The heart?
Yes.
The heart is really something.
What?
Chances of winning are 2%.
3%! Now 4%!
Take-off aborted.
Preparations for haava detonation complete.
I'm on my way!
Why are you coming back?
His one weakness. You remember?
The red heart connecting
the inside and outside.
Who are you talking to?
Stab it with the blade.
The red heart. Then it will stop.
Throw it to me!
I've got it!
Trying to stop us?
You've lived on Earth too long.
Even raising a human child.
Dad!
Let's run away together.
Why'd you come back?
We can lure them back
in time and return here.
Back in time?
Thunder. did you hear?
I did.
Dad!
They're coming!
They'll keep chasing us.
to prevent us from stopping the haava.
Dad. he's behind us!
We can come back before
the haava burst. and stop them.
Let's go to another time.
Ready to transport! Let's go!
Is this Jajang's room?
Are these his clothes?
Jajang's counting the days.
About 3600 so far?
Why's he counting?
Is he waiting for something?
Mr. Blue. Madam Black.
These are our names.
Master Hyun. Dog Thug.
Why are these names here?
Let's see what Jajang burned.
In the year 1381...
Master Hyun's records?
This was 10 years ago.
The sky opened and a flaming
iron cart fell on Yellow Mountain.
Master Hyun witnessed this.
together with the two
sorcerers of Twin Peaks.
That's us!
10 Years Earlier. Yellow Mountain.
What is that?
This is a bad omen.
We should go.
You wait here.
Let's go!
Master Hyun!
What's going on?
It's dangerous. stay here!
That's near my home!
Thunder!
Now let's go back. Thunder.
We must go back... stop... them...
Thunder?
Don't come out.
Dad!
Thunder. go back. quick!
Hurry and go back!
Thunder! Thunder!
Dad!
Chances of winning
10%... 15%... 17%!
Why's it going up?
I'm at my end.
Ean will solve this.
With other people!
I see the future!
I'm trapped in time.
Ean. come back to me!
I'll switch on then.
I need another body.
Need... to find a human...
You woke up.
Where'd you come from?
Your clothes are strange.
Dad?
Thunder!
The energy!
I can't lose it.
Did you see something like a knife?
A knife?
Is it important?
I'll go in.
You wait here.
Who's that?
That's me as a boy.
Why am I there?
Is this a dream?
I remember.
I met a girl by the river.
Was she
the Girl Who Shoots Thunder?
How am I still alive?
Ever caught the mist…
Over a river as the sun is setting?
It's thunder!
Where is it?
Let's go out.
You're getting sleepy.
Why aren't you going to sleep?
Now your body will go limp.
and your eyes will close...
Freeze! It's a charm!
You should've bought
this from us. scoundrel!
Yes. rub your eyes!
It will blind you!
Another charm!
The enchanted bronze mirror.
Should've bought this. too!
And here's a new product.
Mahasuri susuri sabaha.
Surisuri mahasuri susuri sabaha.
Surisuri mahasuri.
What's that?
Isn't it Master Hyun's fan?
Hope the antidote wasn't too bitter.
You lived! Are you okay?
Sure. I'm a dosa!
So. I'll take care of this fellow now.
Careful! They can go into human bodies.
Hold out for a little while.
Not a problem.
I remembered where we met...
Surisuri mahasuri.
That wench hurt her leg!
Serves her right!
I feel great.
That's put me in a great mood.
What's wrong with me?
Taking pleasure in others' pain.
I need further cultivation.
Hey. girl!
Here's the medicine I used
on the thunder you shot at me.
Since it seems we're on the same side.
Sorry about last time.
I'm sure you are.
I'm Madam Black of Twin Peaks.
I'm Ean.
Such a common name.
Banyabaramil!
It came out finally!
Isn't that...
The monster who killed Master Hyun?
I'll take him!
Hot!
It's hot! Hot!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
That's so hot!
Madam!
How'd he get that sword?
Hey. Ean! Ean!
Shoot!
Shoot your thunder through the mirror!
Madam!
Mr. Blue! Watch out!
Hey! Come and get it!
Left Paw. Right Paw!
Follow her!
Okay. 5 minutes have passed!
You've got
something in you. too.
What?
Something inside you...
What's inside me?
Inside you...
It's there...
What's inside me?!
There's no knife.
But is this yours?
Yeah.
What's your name? I'm Muruk.
Ean.
Ean. E-an.
What?
Something scary might come.
I'll go see.
No!
Don't worry.
I'm good with a bow.
I found one.
A human.
In Jajang's room. there were
names of 4 people at Yellow Mountain.
One name was missing.
There was a 5th person.
Who?
Right. Master Hyun
had a young apprentice...
He's become a master dosa.
He pulled the sword from the fan.
Must we kill him. then?
We can come back
before the haava explode.
Now! Let's go!
Let's go to another time.
What is that?
48 minutes until the haava detonate.
The Controller will return.
Escaping the prison of time.
Soon.